gadgethacks.com 2019-11-30

# Privacy Policy « Gadget Hacks

Effective Date: Last revised on May 24, 2018 

The privacy of registered and unregistered users ("users" or "you") is very important to us. This Privacy Policy intends to describe: what type of information we collect; how we use, share, and guard the information and your choices regarding your use of the WonderHowTo, Gadget Hacks, and Next Reality websites and services (the "Website"). 

### Information We Collect

You may choose to provide us with general or specific information about yourself when using the Website, including a user name and email address. Also, we may collect web surfing data such as your IP address, server log data, cookie information, areas of the Website you have visited, and if you clicked on advertisements. We use different types of technologies to collect this information, including cookies and single-pixel GIFs. 

If your browser is configured to accept the cookies, these cookies will be used to recognize your computer when you visit the Website to allow us to provide updates regarding the Website, to learn how you use the Website so that we can develop new services, and to show you advertisements. You can configure your browser to block cookies; however, if you do, the Website may not function properly or at all. 

You may also provide us with personal information. For example, if you choose to register at the Website, you will be asked to create a username and provide a valid email address. If you upload, post, or distribute to the Website information, data, text, photos, audio, links, video, images, graphics, or other content or materials of any nature (collectively, "User Submissions"), those User Submissions, along with your username or other information, may be provided to other users. To limit the amount of personal information disclosed you may consider providing a username other than your actual name. 

### Use and Sharing of Collected Information

We may use non-personally identifiable information collected to improve the quality of the Website; for example, to diagnose problems, assess and maintain security, place ad on webpages receiving more web traffic, and allow you to log in or access your profile information automatically. We may use non-personally identifiable information to determine user demographics, interests, and behavior and may market the Website by sharing non-personally identifiable information with advertisers and other partners. We also may provide your non-personally identifiable information to contractors so that they can perform services for us. 

We use information you provide to: (1) handle or respond to inquiries you initiate with us (such as a customer service request or job application); (2) communicate information that we believe to be of interest to you via email; (3) improve our products and services; (4) fulfill your requests to share information you find on the Website with friends/other parties you have designated; (5) identify relevant advertisements to display. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. 

We may use your information to notify you of important changes to the Website, new services, and special offers. If you do not want to receive such notices, you may opt out as instructed in the WonderHowTo Terms of Use. Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding sales, updates, improvements, or special offers; provided, however that you may not opt-out of receiving notices required by applicable law via email and you hereby agree that our electronic signature on such notices is adequate. If we have provided any third party with your personal information at your election or request, you will have to contact the third-party directly with any opt-out request. If we provide any of the information collected from you with a third party at your election or request, their use of that information will be governed by their privacy policy. For example we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our visitors use the site. You can read more about how Google uses your personal information [here](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). You can also opt-out of Google Analytics [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). 

As the Service provides social functions, we may allow other users to access certain information you provide, such as profile information, your User Submissions, videos you have viewed, and subjects you are interested in. In addition, we allow RSS syndication of all public Service content. 

We may release information, in our sole discretion, in response to the law, a court order, law enforcement request, or investigation or to protect our rights, property, or other interests, including those of our customers or other third parties or to prevent illegal activities or violations of the WonderHowTo Terms of Use. 

In the event that we, in whole or in part, establish a partnership with another company, or are acquired by or merged with another company, collected information may be transferred to the partner or the acquiring or merging company. 

### Changing and Deleting

You can access your personal information through your profile and profile settings on the Website and delete, change or correct information; however, WonderHowTo cannot guarantee that all copies of such information will be immediately deleted from its servers. If you would like to delete your User Submissions in addition to your account, please contact us using the email address provided for privacy questions at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. 

### Child Protection

We do not offer the Website to, or target, persons under the age of 13. In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, any information we receive from people we believe to be under 13 will be purged from our database. 

### Security

We use industry standard security measures to protect against collected information. However, the Internet is not 100% secure and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure. 

### Links to Advertisers and Other Websites

Advertisements and links to third-party advertisers may be displayed on the Website or emailed to you. Third-party ad servers use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Website. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. WonderHowTo does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks WonderHowTo to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. In addition, third-party advertisers may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) and [here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). If you are interested in more information about tailored browser advertising and how you can generally control cookies from being put on your computer to deliver tailored advertising, you may visit the [Network Advertising Initiative’s Consumer Opt-Out link](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices), the [Digital Advertising Alliance’s Consumer Opt-Out link](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/), the [opt-out page of the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/), or [TrustArc's Preference Manager](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) to opt-out of receiving tailored advertising from companies that participate in those programs. You may also use the links available in advertisements that appear on the Website. The information advertisers or other third parties collect is governed by their privacy policies, not by this Privacy Policy. In addition, User Submissions may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of web publishers, advertisers, or other websites that may be linked to the Website. 

In connection with the foregoing, we work with DigiTrust to set a first-party cookie in your browser to enable us and [DigiTrust Partners ](http://www.digitru.st/participating-companies/) to collect web viewing data that includes visits to the Website and non-affiliated websites over time. This data may be used to infer whether you share interests with other users, and deliver advertising relevant to those inferences. Also, third parties whose products or services are accessible or advertised via the Website may place cookies or other tracking technologies on your computer, mobile phone, or other device to collect information about your use of the Website in order to (i) inform, optimize, and serve ads based on past visits to our websites and other sites and (ii) report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our websites and use of our Services. We also allow other third parties (e.g., ad networks and ad servers such as Google Analytics, DoubleClick and others) to serve tailored ads to you on the Services, other sites, and in other applications, and to access their own cookies or other tracking technologies on your computer, mobile phone, or other device you use to access the Services. We neither have access to, nor does this Policy govern, the use of cookies or other tracking technologies that may be placed on your computer, mobile phone, or other device you use to access the Website by non-affiliated, third-party ad technology, ad servers, ad networks or any other non-affiliated third parties. Those parties that use these technologies, including DigiTrust, may offer you a way to opt out of ad targeting as described above. You may receive tailored advertising on your computer through a web browser. 

### Do Not Track

We do not recognize or respond to browser-initiated "Do Not Track" (DNT) signals, as the Internet industry is currently still working toward defining exactly what DNT means, what it means to comply with DNT, and a common approach to responding to DNT. To learn more about Do Not Track, you can do so [here](http://allaboutdnt.com/). 

### Acceptance of Privacy Policy

By using the Website, you are accepting the then-current Privacy Policy, which may be updated from time to time. Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be posted here and are effective upon posting. 

### Questions

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@wonderhowto.com](mailto:privacy@wonderhowto.com) .
